

# ROBERT KIRSZ

Frontend Developer Warsaw, Poland

Email: robert.kirsz@gmail.com

Website: robertkirsz.pl

LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/robertkirsz</u> GitHub: github.com/robertkirsz

#### **SKILLS**

- Experience in building single page applications in React + Redux + React Router using ES6/7 features, bundled together with Webpack
- Writing modular, maintainable CSS with Sass
- Creating fully responsive interfaces
- DOM manipulation with jQuery and native JavaScript
- Knowledge of Bootstrap and Skeleton frameworks
- Experience with Firebase Authentication and Realtime Database
- Basics of creating native mobile apps with React Native
- Familiarity with Scrum workflow
- High attention to writing clean, well formatted code with the help from ESLint
- Gravitating towards functional programming
- Knowledge of Git as a version control system
- Ease of use of Adobe Photoshop for converting PSD files to code
- Knowledge of Windows and macOS systems
- Basic knowledge of Vue framework, Grunt and Gulp build systems
- Familiar with using Trello and ScrumDo platforms

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Native Polish
- Upper intermediate English (B2)
- Beginner German (A1)

#### SUMMARY

Frontend developer especially interested in working with UI and UX, creating rich, involving and accessible app interfaces.

Developed fully functional, responsive applications based on business requirements, delivered in HTML, CSS and JavaScript, mainly using React with Redux.

Participated in projects in all stages of the product lifecycle, from designing to deployment. Gained experience with creating projects from scratch, as well as working with an existing codebase.

Works mostly in Agile and Scrum setting.

Born in 1987, lives in Warsaw, Poland.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### MobileWeb Pro

Gliwice, Poland (remote worker) - since November 2015

Creating web and native applications in React and React Native - from the ground up, as well as adding new functionalities to the existing ones. Working on projects for international clients from Germany, Belgium and United States.

#### K-EX Sp. z o.o.

Warsaw, Poland - February 2012 - March 2015 (3 years and 2 months)

Coordinated logistics of transport and courier parcels for Polkomtel Sp. z o.o.

## P.H.U. Aigel-Tools

Warsaw, Poland - March 2011 - January 2012 (10 months)

Created visual identity for the client, created advertising materials (leaflets, catalogues) using Adobe Photoshop and InDesign

### **Black Tangerine Advertising Agency**

Warsaw, Poland - September 2011 - December 2011 (4 months)

Involved in designing advertising materials for clients (Bakoma and DecoMorreno among others), created website for the agency

#### **EDUCATION**

# Wyższa Szkoła Technologii Informatycznych w Warszawie

(Upper School of Information Technology in Warsaw) 2006 - 2013

Achieved Engineer's Degree in Information Technology Specialization: Computer Graphics and DTP Engineer's Thesis: Creating multimedial web application in HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript

### Liceum Ogólnokształcące nr 79 (ZS nr 48) w Warszawie

(79th High School in Warsaw) 2003 - 2006

Profile: Mathematics and Information Technology